mybudget360.com 2018-05-15

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy refers to www.mybudget360.com

At mybudget360.com we recognize the importance of your personal information.  We never sell personal information to third parties and safeguard your information.

MyBudget360.com does NOT use cookies to collect personal information from your visit.  The only personal information gathered is from visitors who input their e-mail address for the RSS feed which sends out a summary post via e-mail.  No subscription information will be sold or provided to third parties.

Cookies and DoubleClick DART cookies

Our advertisers however MAY use cookies or other technology which might identify preferences about you.  Google, in particular, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website.  The DART cookies are for ads served via DoubleClick help to target ads to your interests.  DART uses “non personally identifiable information.” Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Log Files

A log file collects information from your visit including your internet browser, IP address, and ISP.  As with most websites, this is stored in a log file.  Please be aware that should you disclose personal information in comments, this then becomes public information which other third parties will be able to view.

Return to:  www.mybudget360.com
